Guide to the Julius Bernstein Papers WAG.116
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series III: Unprocessed Materials, 1938-1977
  - Correspondence, reports, publications, and clippings related to Jewish poverty, the Jewish Labor Committee, the Massachusetts State Advisory Committee (United States Commission on Civil Rights), segregation in the construction industry, segregated housing, and Soviet Jewry., 1968-1977 (Box 38)
  - Correspondence, reports, publications, and clippings related to labor unions, protests at Boston schools, Soviet involvement in the Middle East, the Jewish Labor Committee, and the Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee., 1962-1977 (Box 39)
  - Correspondence, reports, publications, and clippings related to desegregating the Boston school system, right-wing extremism in the United States, the Jewish Labor Committee, Soviet Jewry, welfare reform, and unemployment., 1968-1977 (Box 40)